One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Shogun and the Oiran
الشوغن والأويران
Now, I give you one chance to answer my question.
والآن، سأمنحكِ فرصة واحدة للإجابة عن سؤالي
Who are you and what were you doing here?
ما اسمكِ وماذا كنتِ تفعلين؟
If you are honest, I will grant you an instantaneous, painless death.
إن صدقتِ فستكون ميتتك سريعة دون ألم
If you speak falsely, you will face torture most merciless...
أمّا إن كذبتِ، فستتعرضين لتعذيبٍ شديد حتى تعترفي
You know me as...
...اسمي
the Witching Hour Boy.
فتى ساعة السحر
I was investigating how finances flow through the Flower Capital.
أتيت هنا لأكتشف كيف تتدفق الأموال إلى عاصمة الزهور
I see.
هكذا إذًا
So you claim you were doing research on who your next target should be?
أنتِ تدّعين أنكِ أتيتِ لتحديد من سيكون هدفكِ التالي؟
A clever answer...
إجابة ذكية
However, we know you are not who you say you are!
لكننا نعلم أنكِ لم تفصحي عن اسمكِ الحقيقي
I won't let you escape!
لن تهربين
The way you move confirms that you are no common geisha.
تحركاتكِ أثبتت لي أنكِ لستِ مجرد غيشا
You told us you are the Witching Hour Boy to hide your identity and pin this on the thief.
ادّعيتِ أنكِ فتى ساعة السحر لإخفاء هويتك وتلفيق جريمتك بذلك اللص
How cold!
يا للخباثة
Indeed. The Witching Hour Boy was just spotted in the capital.
صحيح، فقد ظهر فتى ساعة السحر في العاصمة قبل قليل
Let me ask one more time.
سأكرر سؤالي
Who are you? What were you doing here?
ما اسمكِ؟ وماذا كنتِ تفعلين؟
I had no idea you were so fond of being tortured.
يبدو أنكِ مصرّة على خيار التعذيب
So be it!
...في هذه الحالة
Begin!
عليكم بها
What?!
ماذا؟
She vanished?!
اختفت؟
Where did she go?
أين ذهبت؟
That could have been dire if I hadn't used a clone.
كانت لتكون نهايتي لو لم أكن استخدم نسخة
This is Orobi!
هنا أوروبي
Onami! Shinobu! Bonekichi!
أونامي وشينوبو-سان والعظمي-كيتشي
I apologize. The enemy discovered me!
اعذروني، كُشف أمري
– What?
ماذا؟ كشفوا روبين؟
Oh no! This is a big problem!
يا للهول، هذه مصيبة
It's hard to believe they would find Orobi!
لا أصدق أنهم كشفوا أمر أوروبي-سان
There are ninja in the castle! At least eleven by my count!
ثمة نينجا في القلعة وعددهم 11 على الأقل
Eleven ninja?!
11؟
Fukurokuju!
فوكوروكوجو
Fukurokuju is the leader of a ninja unit.
فوكوروكوجو هو قائد فرقة النينجا
They are the Orochi Oniwabanshu, an elite force!
إنهم نخبة النينجا ويُطلق عليهم أونيابانشو أوروتشي
I'm sure they'll go after Orobi! Let's protect her, Onami!
لا بدّ أنهم سيسعون خلف أوروبي، لنذهب لحمايتها يا أونامي
Okay! Robin, where are you?!
حسنًا، روبين، أين أنتِ الآن؟
Hey! You're a geisha, right?
مهلًا، أنتِ غيشا
Oh, yes!
أ-أجل
What're you doing out here? Oops...
ماذا تفعلين هنا؟
Easy there. Please watch your step.
عجبًا، تمالك نفسك
I got so drunk...
شربتُ حتى الثمالة
I gotta go to the bathroom...
عليّ الذهاب إلى الحمام
I'll take a leak so I can drink some more!
سأتبول الآن حتى أتمكن من شرب المزيد
We lost the signal.
انقطع الاتصال
We have to find her ourselves.
علينا البحث عنها
Brook, did you hear that?
بروك، هل سمعتنا؟
Find and protect Robin.
ابحث عن روبين واحمها
Okay, okay! I got it.
حاضر، مفهوم
And here I finally got to do something other than gathering food...
لم يحدث هذا إلا عندما وجدت شيئًا أفعله غير جمع الطعام
A curse on you!
!يا للنحس
Was she a ninja?
أكانت نينجا؟
Or perhaps a specter?
أم ربما شبح؟
It doesn't matter if it was ninjutsu or magic, her real body must be nearby.
لا يهمنا إن كان نينجتسو أو سحرًا، فالجسد الحقيقي قريب
Listen up!
تذكروا
Shogun Orochi is holding a banquet!
يُقيم أوروتشي-ساما مأدبة الآن
Let's not raise a ruckus over one measly rat!
إياكم إثارة جلبة بسبب دخيلة نكرة
– Yes, sir!
حاضر
Now, let's drink some more...!
والآن، لنشرب المزيد
Oh, no, you mustn't overdo it.
عجبًا، لا تُفرط في الشرب
Oh, how lovely!
!يا للمتعة
Oh, it's the new girl Orobi! Where have you been?!
الجارية الجديدة أوروبي، أين كنتِ؟
Come over here!
اقتربي
Yes, my lord!
حـ-حاضرة
"A wise man hides a leaf in the forest."
"الحكيم يخبئ ورقة شجر في الغابة"
Escape is no longer an option, but I still have tasks to carry out.
الخروج من هنا مستحيل حاليًّا، ولكن لا يزال لدي دور عليّ إنجازه
I'm sorry...
...المعذرة
I took so long...
تأخرت عليك
my lord!
يا مولاي
Even if I get bone-tired—because I'm all bones—I'll keep looking for her.
سأبحث عنها حتى آخر قطرة عرق رغم أنني مجرد هيكل عظمي
Is she here?
أهي هنا؟
Or here?
أم هنا؟
Ah! Crud!
هذا سيئ
Who are you?!
من أنت؟
Halt!
انتظر
What are you doing over there?!
ماذا تفعل عندك؟
Oh?
ماذا؟
Where did they go?!
أين ذهب؟
You saw me!
رأيتماني
S-S-Something's here!
شـ-شـ-شيء ما هنا
It's a specter!
إنه شبح
Wow! So, all those wonderful treasures will be taken to Onigashima?
رائع، ستأخذ هذه الكنوز معك إلى أونيغاشيما؟
That's right!
بكل تأكيد
Do you want to hear more about the Fire Festival, Orobi?
أتريدين معرفة المزيد عن مهرجان النار يا أوروبي؟
Oh, yes, I want to hear so much more about you.
أجل، أريد التعرف عليك أكثر فأكثر
In that case, how would you like to be in the running to become my primary consort?
أيعني هذا أنكِ تريدين منافسة البقية لتكوني عشيقتي؟
Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي
My lord plays with my heart...
لقد جرحت مشاعري-أرينسو
Don't pout, don't pout, Komurasaki!
لا تعبسي، لا تعبسي يا كوموراساكي
My cute, darling dearest!
ما أجملكِ، يا لظرافتك
Is Shogun Orochi...
...أوروتشي-ساما
aware that there is another side to her?
ألا يعرف الجانب المظلم من كوموراساكي؟
Even if he knew, he would overlook it because of her beauty.
حتى إن عرف، فلن يلومها بفضل جمالها الذي أسر قلبه
How adorable!
ما أجملكِ
Oh, it's nothing...
لا شيء
Here you go, my Lord!
تفضل يا مولاي
Sake really hits the spot when Komurasaki serves it!
الساكي من يديّ كوموراساكي مذاقه في النخاع
Our top oiran Komuraski... What a beauty!
المحظية كوموراساكي، إنها آية في الجمال
I wish I were Shogun Orochi...
كم أغبط أوروتشي-ساما
but that darker side of hers truly frightens me!
لكنني أخشى جانبها المظلم
Forget about it! She'd never go for you anyway!
لا تقلق، لن تقع في حبك أصلًا
Right?!
صحيح؟
She's had more training than any of the other women from your pleasure hall,
وأيضًا، أي امرأة من منطقة الملذات خاصتك لا بدّ من أن تكون مدربة جيدًا
Boss Kyoshiro.
أليس كذلك أيها الزعيم كيوشيرو؟
You shouldn't confuse a courtesan with a pet dog.
يجب ألّا تخلط بين المحظية والكلب الأليف
People are flowers.
المرء كالأزهار
Unless you are clean water, a lady will not bloom elegantly.
ذوي السقيا الطاهرة هم من يجعلون زهرةً مثلها تتفتّح
You got us there!
نلت منا في كلامك
But I heard you sent the Soaring Six just to take down a soba cook!
بالمناسبة، سمعت أنك أرسلت التوبي روبو لمجرد النيل من طاهي سوبا
You're as merciless as ever!
أنت صارم كالعادة
We yakuza become parents to our underlings once we exchange cups of sake.
نحن الياكوزا نعدّ أي شخص يحتسي معنا الساكي فردًا من عائلتنا
If your kid came home beaten up, what would you do?
إن أتى ابنك إليك يشكو ضربًا مبرحًا، فماذا ستفعل؟
I've always been in awe of your chivalrous spirit.
طالما كنتُ معجبًا بشهامتك أيها الزعيم
You're absolutely right, Kyoshiro!
معك حق يا كيوشيرو
You must always crush your enemy with overwhelming force!
عليك أن تبطش بأعدائك دومًا
It ensures that they never rise back up against you!
لتضمن ألّا يتجرأ أحدهم عليك أبدًا
Even if they happen to be...
...حتى وإن كانوا
ghosts!
أشباحًا
Your lackeys getting beaten is just the tip of the iceberg.
لم يقتصر الأمر على هزيمة أتباعك فحسب
Kyoshiro.
يا كيوشيرو
Outsiders are infiltrating the capital!
تسلل بعض الغرباء إلى العاصمة
Listen, up! Since I have you all here, I'll say it once more!
اسمعوا جميعًا، سأقول هذا لمرة واحدة بمناسبة جمعنا اليوم
Twenty years have passed since the death of Kozuki Oden!
تُصادف هذه السنة الذكرى العشرين لموت أودين
His wife Toki said that this would be the year of their vengeance!
وقالت زوجته توكي إنّ الانتقام سيحين هذه السنة
Oden's legacy persists!
ما تزال إرادة أودين حية
It's that old ghost story again...
...قصة الأشباح مجددًا
Who even remembers the Kozuki anymore...?
باتت عشيرة الكوزكي في طيّ النسيان الآن
Don't you agree, Komurasaki?
ألا توافقيني يا كوموراساكي؟
Remember how formidable Oden's Nine Red Scabbards were?!
أتذكرون مدى قوة أغماد أودين التسعة؟
Their leader, Kin'emon, is exceptionally cunning!
وقائدهم كينيمون في غاية الحنكة
Twenty years later, they have returned to Wano and are conspiring their plot!
لقد عادوا إلى وانو بعد عشرين سنة، وها هم يستعدون للانتقام
They will come...
...سوف يأتون
to take my head!
لقطع رأسي
We've already buried a good deal of people related to Oden...
دفن عددًا لا يُحصى من معارف أودين سلفًا
but he's still afraid of the Kozuki Clan?
ولا يزال خائفًا من عشيرة الكوزكي؟
Even though Kaido just took down one of our enemies,
...صحيح أنّ كايدو هزم أحد الأعداء
it wasn't before a yokozuna and some of Jack's men were attacked in Kuri!
ولكن ثمة من هاجم اليوكوزونا ورجال جاك في مقاطعة كوري
There's the soba cook from the capital and the ronin from the post town who both attacked our yakuza!
طاهي السوبا في العاصمة
It could've all been done on Kin'emon's orders!
ربما يكون كينيمون المسؤول عن تلك الهجمات
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Red Scabbards...
إن أتى ثعلب النار كينيمون ومعه ساموراي الأغماد
I cannot wait to face them!
فأنا أتحرّق شوقًا لمقابلتهم
I will cut them down with a single stroke!
سأريك مدى مهارتي في القطع
How dependable you are, Kyoshiro!
أنت لها يا كيوشيرو
Oden died right before my eyes!
شهدتُ موت أودين بأم عيني
But his son Momonosuke is still alive!
ولكن ابنه مومونوسكي لا يزال حيًّا
That brat's body wasn't found with the rest!
لم يُعثر على جثة ذلك الشقي مع البقية
The Kozuki line lives on!
لم يمت جميع أفراد عشيرة الكوزكي بعد
Their goal is no less than the restoration of the Kozuki Clan...
يتمثّل هدفهم في إعادة عشيرة الكوزكي للحكم
Of course, they'll attempt to behead Kaido, too.
وسيسعون إلى قطع رأس كايدو أيضًا
They will definitely come!
سيأتون حتمًا
No one could chop off Kaido's head!
لا أحد يستطيع قتل كايدو
Can he be any more cowardly?!
إلى أي درجة هو جبان؟
You're drinking too much!
أفرطتَ في الشرب
It'll be your head if he hears you!
إن سمع كلامك، فأنت من سيُقطع رأسه
Otoko, take this one next!
أوتوكو-تشان، خذي هذه تاليًا
Okay!
حاضرة
Hey, I'm out of sake!
نفد الساكي عندنا
Yes, we'll be right with you!
حاضرة، سنحضر المزيد
Can you take it to him?!
هلّا تأخذينه إليه؟
Yes, ma'am!
حاضرة
I'm telling you, this is the year!
أصغوا إليّ جميعًا، إنها السنة الموعودة
Remember Toki's last words!
تذكروا كلمات توكي الأخيرة
Be on your guard!
إياكم الاستهانة بالأمر
He's so paranoid.
إنه خائف للغاية
It's pathetic.
مثير للشفقة
When will he realize that poem is pure nonsense?
إلى متى سيظل مؤمنًا بصحة تلك القصيدة السخيفة؟
"You are the moon, unaware of the approach of daybreak."
"أيا قمرًا غافلًا عن دنو الفجر"
Here we go again... Now the sake is ruined.
ها قد بدأ مجددًا، سيُفسد علينا مذاق الساكي
"May your purpose be fulfilled...
"إن كانت بك رغبةٌ تواقة لتحقيقها"
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of twenty years.
"حين تلتقي تسعة ظلال محبوكة معًا بعد عشرين سنة في ليلةٍ مقمرة"
Then you shall know the brilliance of dawn!"
"ولتعرفنّ حينها رونق ضِياء الفجر"
The meaning is clear!
أنتم تعرفون معنى هذا
After twenty years, on a moonlit night,
سيحين وقت الانتقام في ليلة مقمرة بعد عشرين سنة
the ghosts of those nine samurai will come...
إذ سيظهر تسعة ساموراي بهيئة أشباح للنيل مني
and enact their vengeance by killing me...
مما يعني أنهم سيقتلوني
and in doing so open Wano!
وسيفتحون بلاد وانو
Orochi is very set in his belief of the prophecy...
يؤمن أوروتشي إيمانًا راسخًا بصحة تلك النبوءة
But his subordinates don't seem to take it seriously.
وبالمقابل يظن أتباعه أنها محض أوهام
That's not surprising.
لا عجب
He's so delusional...
إنه واهم
Oden and the Red Scabbards are all dead!
أودين والأغماد قد ماتوا سلفًا
They're not even a memory for me.
أنا بالكاد أتذكرهم
We won't allow them to come and do as they please!
لن ندعهم يحققون مسعاهم
We cannot afford to lower our guard...
لهذا لا يجدر بنا التهاون
Who's doing that? Cut it out, idiot!
من هذا؟ اخرس يا غبي
You can't laugh! Hold it in!
لا تضحكي، توقفي
Who was that?!
من ضحك؟
Did someone actually laugh at me?!
أيعقل أنها ضحكة ساخرة مني؟
Otoko!
أوتوكو-تشان
Everyone thinks he's a fool!
الجميع يظنونه أحمق
Cut it out! Just leave already!
هذا يكفي، غادر
I can't stop! I'm so sorry!
لا يمكنني التوقف، المعذرة
– It's a child! – She's the oiran's attendant!
إنها طفلة
Stop her!
أوقفوها
Otoko!
أوتوكو-تشان
I know I shouldn't laugh!
أعلم أنه لا يجدر بي الضحك
How distasteful!
يا للوقاحة
I am the shogun!
أنا الشوغن
Stop her!
أوقفوها
A twenty-year-old grudge...
...ضغينة مضى عليها عشرين سنة
Do you actually think...?
...أتظنين أنني
Do you think it frightens me?!
أتظنين أنني خائف منها؟
I am the victor!
أنا المنتصر
My lord!
مولاي
I defeated Oden!
انتصرت على أودين
Please! Stop it!
أرجوكِ توقفي
Stop this!
إياك
The oiran!
الأويران
It's useless!
لا يمكنها المساعدة
That black-hearted woman can't do anything!
ماذا يمكن لامرأة ماكرة فعله؟
My lord!
مولاي
She is but a child.
إنها مجرد طفلة-أرينسو
Stay out of this, Komurasaki!
اصمتي يا كوموراساكي
My lord, please forgive her!
مولاي، سامحها رجاءً
You dare laugh at me?!
أكنتِ تضحكين عليّ؟
You whelp!
متعجرفة
She's prone to laughter! She means no offense!
إنها تضحك دائمًا، لم تكن تقصد السخرية
There's no stopping him now! Forget about her!
فات الأوان على إيقافه، انسي أمرها
My lord! She's just a child! Have mercy!
مولاي، إنها مجرد طفلة، ارحمها
Listen to me when I speak!
أتصغين إليّ؟
Stop laughing!
كفاكِ ضحكًا
Otoko!
أوتوكو-تشان
Komurasaki...
...كوموراساكي
Why...?
لماذا؟
How could you strike me?
لماذا صفعتني؟
Apologize, Komurasaki!
اعتذري يا كوموراساكي
Bow until your forehead sinks into the floor!
اركعي وطأطئي رأسك أمام حضرته
I refuse!
لن أفعل-أرينسو
I will never abase myself before anyone!
أنا لن أركع لأي شخص كائنًا من كان
How dare she!
كيف تجرؤ؟
When I know I am right, I have no need to even give an inch!
ولن أتراجع طالما أنّ الحق معي
Hey, Komurasaki...
...يا... كوموراساكي
I was going to make you...
...كنتُ أنوي
the wife of the shogun.
جعلكِ زوجة الشوغن
If you would prefer a weak woman...
إن كنت تريد امرأة خنوعة
then please, take your blade to my flesh!
فتفضّل واقطعني الآن
I am the daughter of a samurai!
أنا ابنة ساموراي
Silence!
اصمتي
I will not live in disgrace!
لن أعيش ذليلة
How impertinent...!
...يا لوقاحتك
You're nothing more than a whore!
أنتِ مجرد عاهرة مبجلة
Don't act like you know a damn thing about the ways of the samurai!
لا يحق لكِ التحدث عن كبرياء الساموراي
Shogun Orochi...?!
أوروتشي-ساما؟
He transformed.
لقد تحول
Komurasaki...
كوموراساكي
Mythical Snake Snake Fruit: Yamata no Orochi
فاكهة الثعبان نوع: ياماتا نو أوروتشي (زون أسطوري)
What a waste...
...يا للأسف
It'd be a shame to lose such beauty!
من المؤسف خسارة هذا الجمال
I'd rather not chew up your head!
وجهك يمنعني من سحق رأسك
Apologize!
اعتذري
If you beg for your life,
إن توسلتِ إليّ لحياتك
you will get a lighter sentence!
فسأرأف بكِ
What are you waiting for?!
ماذا تنتظرين؟
Apologize from the bottom of your heart!
اعتذري من صميم قلبك
You should learn to let things go...
يجب أن تتعلم التخلّي عن ما تتعلق به
They say whoever falls in love loses.
يقال إنّ من الحب ما قتل
What?!
ماذا؟
I...
...أنا
will not beg for my life!
لن أتوسل لحياتي
She's provoking him...
إنها تستفزه
Stop it, Komurasaki!
كفى يا كوموراساكي
Komurasaki!
كوموراساكي
Damn you!
أيتها اللعينة
Shogun Orochi, why are you attacking us?!
أوروتشي-ساما، لماذا تهاجمنا؟
How insolent!
أيتها الوقحة
Huh? Aren't you the lady from the soba shop?!
هل أنتِ الأخت التي التقيتها عند محل السوبا؟
Otoko! I'm glad you're okay.
أوتوكو-تشان، سعيدة أنكِ بخير
Where did that sorceress go?!
أين ذهبت تلك الساحرة؟
Hold it right there!
هذه نهايتك
You thought you could deceive us?!
كيف تجرؤين على خداعنا؟
I found the woman!
وجدت تلك المرأة
Very well, Komurasaki!
لكِ ذلك يا كوموراساكي
As you wish,
كما تشائين
I will kill you with my own hands!
سأقتلكِ بنفسي
Verily, this is pandemonium!
يا للصخب
Prepare yourself!
...استعدي
Komurasaki!
يا كوموراساكي
Daikoku!
دايكوكو
Why aren't you ninja stopping the shogun?!
عليكم أيها النينجا إيقاف الشوغن
Save the oiran!
أنقذوا الأويران
He's free to do what he wants. Nothing can stop him.
الشوغن حُر، لا قيود لتصرفاته
More importantly,
الأهم من ذلك
we're currently dealing with an intruder!
نحن نتعامل مع دخيلة حاليًّا
An intruder?!
دخيلة؟
Orobi is an intruder?
أوروبي-سان دخيلة؟
Come to think of it, I've never seen her before now!
بالتفكير بالأمر، لم أرها من قبل
Hey, lady, please save the oiran.
يا أختاه، أنقذي الأويران
I can't!
لا يمكنني
I don't even know if I can save you after the way you angered the shogun!
ولا أعلم إن كنت قادرة على إنقاذكِ بعدما أغضبتِ الشوغن
Help us!
النجدة
It's a curse of death!
سيقتلنا بلعنته
What's going on over there?!
ما تلك الجلبة؟
Fujin! Raijin! What's going on?!
فوجين، رايجين، ما بالكما؟
I-It's a specter!
إ-إنه شبح
The gashadokuro yokai really exists!
اتضح أنّ غاشادوكورو ليس خرافة غاشادوكورو = هيكل عظمي جائع شبح يظهر ليلًا حسب الخرافات اليابانية
A curse on you!
سألعنكم
A ghost!
شبح
Otoko!
أوتوكو-تشان
A curse on you!
سألعنكم
Robin, I'm glad you're all right!
سعيد بسلامتك يا روبين-سان
Bonekichi, you're a hero! Thanks!
أنت رائع أيها العظمي-كيتشي، شكرًا
I'm awesome, am I?
أقلتِ إنني رائع؟
Keep it up!
واصل إخافتهم رجاءً
Let's get out of here!
لنخرج من هنا
Are they allied with the specter?!
هل هم حلفاء الشبح؟
Mil Fleurs!
ألف زهرة ميل فلور
Gigantesco Mano!
اليد العملاقة غيغانتيسكو مانو
How could you...?!
كيف تجرؤين؟
Damn you!
أيتها اللعينة
I have her!
لن تهربي
Th-The gashadokuro!
غا-غاشادوكورو
Allow me to guide you to the land of the dead,
...دعيني أرشدكِ إلى أرض الموتى
young lady!
يا آنسة
Go away!
ابتعد
It's both Robin and Brook...
...روبين وحتى بروك
What should we do?!
ما العمل؟
There's no point in staying hidden.
لا جدوى من الاختباء الآن
The Castle Attic
علية القلعة
Let's go!
لنذهب لمساندتهما
Understood, Shinobu!
مفهوم يا شينوبو-تشان
Who's there?! A ninja?!
من هناك؟ نينجا؟
Hey, miss! She just called you "Shinobu," didn't she?!
نادتك هذه المرأة باسم شينوبو، صحيح؟
Is that you...
...أنت
Hanzo?!
هانزو
So you're alive! The man-seducing...
إذًا فأنتِ على قيد الحياة يا غاوية الرجال
sexy kunoichi.
الكونويتشي الجذابة
Shinobu the Man-Killer!
قاتلة الرجال" شينوبو"
How did you know?
عرفتني إذًا
No, you're not her.
لا، لستِ هي
Forget it!
انسي الأمر
It is me!
أنا هي
Ninpo: Ballbuster!
فنون النينجا: سحق الخصيتان نينبو كينتاما تسوبوشي
That was ninjutsu?!
أكان ذلك نينجتسو؟
This is why... you're known as... the Man-Killer.
لهذا... تُلقبّين... بقاتلة الرجال
That's why?!
أهذا المقصود من لقبك؟
I-I can't move...
أ-أعجز عن الحراك
Ninpo: Paralysis Technique!
فنون النينجا: تقنية الشلل نينبو كاناشيباري نو جتسو
What?! You just made that up!
اخترعتِ هذا الاسم توًّا
We have to get going!
علينا الإسراع
Let's go, Onami!
لنذهب يا أونامي
Sexy Ninpo:
فنون النينجا المثير سكسي نينبو
Rot Garden!
حديقة العفن كاري سان سوي
Why did Hanzo fall down from the attic?
لماذا سقط هانزو من العلية؟
Who are those two kunoichi?!
من هاتان الكونويتشي؟
What's going on?!
ما الذي يحدث؟
The banquet room is a mess!
عمّت الفوضى قاعة المأدبة
Whoa, Onami!
مرحبًا يا أونامي-سان
A curse on you!
سألعنكِ
Why on me?!
لماذا؟
Onami!
أونامي
I'm here to help!
أتيت لمساندتكما
Where are you, Komurasaki?!
أين أنتِ يا كوموراساكي؟
There you are!
وجدتكِ
Kyoshiro?!
كيوشيرو؟
You should not have done that, Komurasaki...
فعلتِها هذه المرة بالفعل يا كوموراساكي
Are you prepared?
مستعدة؟
I am.
نعم
Big Sis...!
...أختاه
Boss Kyoshiro, why did you do that?
كيوشيرو-دونو، لِمَ فعلت هذا؟
She was the most beautiful woman in Wano...!
...أجمل امرأة في وانو
This is heartrending!
يا للأسف
Komurasaki...
...كوموراساكي
What have you done, Kyoshiro?!
ما الذي فعلته يا كيوشيرو؟
Did I tell you to kill her?!
أنا لم آمرك بقتلها
You upstart...!
أيها الوغد
This was...
...طبّقتُ على كوموراساكي
a samurai's act of mercy for Komurasaki.
رحمة الساموراي
Defying the shogun is a grave crime, regardless of one's status!
من يتمرد على الشوغن يُعدم كائنًا من كان
That law is ironclad.
هذه قاعدة لا تقبل النقاش
He did it as a show of loyalty?!
أفعل هذا لإثبات مدى ولائه؟
Kyoshiro has gone too far...
تمادى كيوشيرو كثيرًا
Give me...
...سلّميني
that whelp!
تلك المتعجرفة
I will chew her to death!
سأقتلها بأنيابي
If you hadn't laughed at me, she wouldn't have had to die!
لولا ضحكتها الساخرة مني لما ماتت كوموراساكي
You brat!
متعجرفة
Hand her over, Orobi!
سلّميني إياها يا أوروبي
Who the hell are you anyway?!
ومن تكونين أصلًا؟
Robin!
روبين
Get out here, Zeus!
اخرج يا زيوس
Hey! Did you call for me, Nami?
مرحبًا، هل استدعيتني يا نامي؟
I want to give you some weather eggs.
سأعطيك بيضة طقس
Yeah?!
حقًّا؟
A curse on you...
سألعنكم
This is no time for us to be chased by a ghost!
هذا ليس وقتًا مناسبًا ليطاردنا شبح
Why isn't it attacking?!
لماذا لا يهاجمنا؟
A curse on you!
سألعنكم
Oh, dear! They noticed!
هذا سيئ، اكتشفوا الأمر
Guess it's time to go.
حان وقت مغادرتي
It's time to fight!
اخرجوا وقاتلوا
There is trouble in the banquet hall!
ثمة مشكلة في قاعة المأدبة
Capture the intruders and exorcise the yokai!
اقبضوا على الدخلاء وتخلّصوا من الشبح
Contain Shogun Orochi's rampage!
وأوقفوا هيجان أوروتشي-ساما
Everyone, hit the deck!
انبطحوا جميعًا
Ninpo:
فنون النينجا نينبو
Thunderbolt!
صاعقة رايتي
What the hell?!
ما هذا؟
You're young, but that was one impressive ninpo!
ما زلتِ يافعة، لكنه كان أسلوب نينجا مدهش
That was close!
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Only you could've pulled it off, Onami!
كما عهدناكِ يا أونامي
The Next Morning Okobore Town Kuri, Wano Nine Days Until the Final Battle
في اليوم التالي بلدة أوكوبوري في مقاطعة كوري وانو تبقت تسعة أيام !!على المعركة النهائية
Have some oshiruko. Go ahead, Olin, try it!
تفضلي يا أولين-سان
Wow! It smells delicious!
رائحته طيبة
Thank you!
شكرًا على الطعام
It's yummy!
لذيذ
This red bean soup is so sweet and tasty!
مذاق هذا الأوشيروكو حلوٌ ولذيذ
I'm glad that you like it.
يسعدني أنه أعجبكِ
I'm sorry, Olin, but that's all we had.
اعذرينا يا أولين-سان ولكن ما عندنا إلا هذا القدر
I wish I could have more.
صحيح أنني أرغب بالمزيد
But you fed me even though you barely have anything. Thank you, Miss Tsuru.
لكنكِ أطعمتني رغم فقرك، شكرًا لكِ يا تسورو-سان
Is she really that strong?
هل هي قوية؟
Yeah, stronger than you'll ever know...
أجل، قوية جدًّا
Then let's get her to rescue Big Bro from the prison in Udon!
إذًا فأريد منها إنقاذ أخي الكبير المحتجز في مقاطعة أودون
Oh, that's a great idea!
أجل، فكرة سديدة
It's not that easy!
الأمر ليس بهذه البساطة
She'll never listen to us!
لن تستمع إلينا أبدًا
Let's do this, Chopperemon!
لنذهب يا تشوبايمون
Let's go!
لنذهب
Are you sure? If she gets her memory back, we're done for!
أواثقون من هذا؟ سيُقضى علينا حالما تستعيد ذاكرتها
It's better than just waiting here!
هذا أفضل من البقاء هنا
I want to go! This is our chance!
أريد استغلال هذه الفرصة
Um...
...المعذرة
What is it, cute little Chopperemon?
ماذا تريد يا تشوبايمون الظريف؟
Put 'er there.
صافحني
O-Okay...
حـ-حاضر
I'm hungry...
أنا جائعة
I wanna eat more...
أريد أكل المزيد
I'm seriously scared!
مخيفة جدًّا
We need your help. Olin.
نحتاج إلى مساعدتكِ يا أولين
Let's go to Udon together!
لنذهب معًا إلى مقاطعة أودون
Udon? That's where I'm going?
أودون؟ أكنت ذاهبة إلى هناك؟
Indeed!
أجل
I heard the Superstar in charge of Udon loves oshiruko!
سمعتُ أنّ النجم البارز المسؤول عن مقاطعة أودون يحب حساء الأوشيروكو
Yeah, that's right! They have tons of red-bean soup there!
صحيح، صحيح لديهم كثير من حساء الأوشيروكو
That lie just slipped out...
كذبت تلقائيًّا
If there's no oshiruko there,
...إن لم نجد أوشيروكو هناك
she'll kill me!
فستقتلني
There's tons of red-bean soup there?!
ثمة كثير من الأوشيروكو هناك؟
Then let's get a move on!
لنذهب حالًا